I'm Taken! This is our butterfly tokey!
Yes, that's right.
I haven't had this greeting in a while.
Chow Tube.
To talk like this on my own.
Maybe for the first time? (one's) first time
In this opening.
Well, I'm doing something I'm not quite used to.
We are at the futsal field today.
With Guests
I would like to play futsal.
Well, I'd like to invite our guest to join us right away.
I think, he's the one.
abbr. of particle "ni" (used especially when it precedes the verb "naru")
Oh, pro-soccer space, it was shaped like a film!
I'm not a professional, but my touch on the ball was far from professional.
ahaha
I've been driving around on Miruku's channel.
I'm doing the first half of the drive on Mirukun's side.
If you haven't already, I guess I should look at that one before I look at this one.
Hello. - Hello.
be a kite shaped like a octopus
Do it right until the ninth grade and then do it from high school on.
Did you find something you liked?
My favorite.
I love chiraco ponzu so much!
I've recently learned to eat chilaco ponzu.
Thank you for watching!
I drove in with a couple of people, but yes.
We're getting closer, but I'm not sure if he's paying attention to me yet.
Start at about 30 per. That's more than I expected.
I don't know what's making me sad, so after this... we'll just keep on monkeying around.
I brought a project to ask you to raise the percentage.
Is Yes a Silence in Pukkal
grumbling
No boo-boo's! Let's get closer to each other AND GATTY TIGER!
I'm not too used to it, after all, it's the hardest thing to do with each of them.
I don't care if you say it's too early for a session.
Boom, boom, boom, boom. Kick the ball around.
Well, I'm just going to do a little upload, you know, pass and stuff.
I think I'll take it gradually.
When did you start?
Kindergarten, middle of the year, I guess.
I've been here about 10 years.
Maybe the same. 11 years. About 10 years.
What position did you play?
Position: I was mostly in the volanti position.
Like a top down volante.
I'm the type of person who makes games. I'm the type of person who makes games.
I'm not very smart.
I was more of a commanding presence, if you will.
Heh.
I have experience with all of them.
Oh, really?
There's even a keeper.
What? Oh, yeah.
I've been allowed to do all kinds of things.
I broke my pinky finger when I played keeper.
That's why I quit.
I'm definitely a keeper, so I decided not to.
I was much less sexual and smaller then.
There's no way a guy like that could stop it.
a-ha-ha-ha (laughing loudly)
I've been a forward most of my life, but I was a forward who didn't score, so I was the decoy type.
I'm not doing it at all. I heard that you used to have a birthday party or something like that.
No, it was just the one time, and at that time Spadra and others came, and the warehouse was still this small, seriously, that level, seriously. We've been playing a lot of futsal, but we haven't played since this year.
I come here often. What do you do? I was invited to play soccer by a friend of mine who's a YouTube star, and I've been to some of those actor-acting events. A soccer team has been started.
What does that mean? I made the uniforms. Your uniforms? You mean your own team with your own fans? I'm thinking of participating in a tournament. Wait, wait, what do you mean? So far we only have Shunta Sono and Hayate as our members Spatara, I'm thinking of making my own team.
Why are you fighting them? Who do you want to play? I'd like to play a weak team, because if we don't play a weak team, there's a chance we'll lose, but now that our throats and our bodies are warmed up, we've prepared a game to warm up both, mainly our throats. What's this?
We'll have five themes, and you'll kick yourself over to what you want to talk about, and then we'll go into more depth about it, and then we'll talk to each other about it.
The talk theme is music, friends, dreams, worries, acting, and no heavy rubbing.
Very heavy Very heavy content
It's like we're talking to the right person. I knew it. I'm looking forward to it.
What should I aim for? Aiming is important.
Whether you say it or not, it's cooler to say it.
It would be cool if you guessed it.
It's all about the music, isn't it?
Something nice.
There's a PK routine I've been doing since I was in the service.
I have.
I'm a one-step PK, I swear.
What?
So here's a step in this direction.
I've been saying for a long time that we need to shift the timing.
Okay, let's go.
Aim for the music.
I'm going for the music.
Okay, look.
Then the first one of 10.
Watch your right quite a bit.
Last left.
To the left.
I thought that meant he'd kick this way, but he kicked this way.
I got it off!
It would have been nice if it had been a regular PK... the course.
I was just getting ready to go.
I have to hit it.
Oh, I see.
It was floating, to begin with.
Yeah, I was floating. I was floating. I was floating.
More, just a golfer.
Oh, Goro. Wow, I did it.
♪ You'll swim with me ♪
- I'm just asking for a minute. - I've never been a little off the mark.
I don't care about PK routines or anything else.
- I don't know what I'll do.
I'll just go ahead and say what I'm aiming for.
He said he's almost 30 and has more problems than ever.
I'll make it a problem!
Wow!
- Yum! - That's what I'm talking about.
- It's good! - Might be cool.
♪ ~
Now that's cool. Seriously.
You've been shown your seniority. Completely.
I don't need that kind of PK routine or anything like that.
Oh, no.
It already fits.
I like to call it PK on the other hand.
It's okay to use goro.
Yes.
Okay, here it is. Here it is. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Elibaly, I'm not in trouble.
You wanted to see me.
What would you like one more?
I'd like you to tell me about your dream.
What?
dream
I thought I was dreaming too.
I'd love to talk about it.
I want to talk about it.
please
good
appetizing
Good, good, good, too good.
right in the center (center)
Thank you for your hard work.
I put on the music.
My problems and dreams
heavy
The heavy ones.
So I'm going to talk on a theme regarding these three.
Yes, let's talk.
please
Yes, sir.
Cash Tiger in Both Houses
Thank you for your hard work.
Actually, there's a convenience store movie in the works. I forgot about it and just used it.
I should have done it at the opening.
I think we'll start with the lightest music.
Let's go. Let's go.
First, a question about music.
What is important to you as an artist?
No, thank you. We'll make it.
Light, isn't it?
Light, huh? Light, huh? Make it. Make it.
What is important to you as an artist?
Yeah, what do you got?
Well, I guess so.
Um, as an idol, I would never be on stage.
Um, it's like it keeps sparkling.
I think I'm probably aware of it.
Are you sleepy?
No, no, no, I wasn't listening. I was being serious.
I was being serious.
I guess that's what it sounds like.
-end-.
Well, as an idol, you're supposed to keep on sparkling, and that's what I value.
Not dressing up in any way, just being yourself.
So it's rather something like this.
For example, when the camera comes in close, like this.
Like, there's some kind of production like a decisive face.
I don't want to be too honest.
I wonder what it's called.
And of course, that's something important, too.
The customer probably saw it.
It's important to have a point of view that makes people go "caw".
Anything is a balancing act.
But something like this.
I'm not very good at saying, "I'm the one!" I'm not very good at that.
I want to always be this way.
You know, other members and stuff.
As a pretty super-expressive who's who.
Some of us are the type of people who are properly on stage.
It's a little bit like you're wearing something.
I'd like to see one with a filter on it.
I have no more filters or anything.
To be who you are.
I think it's something I cherish.
I know.
When I went to a live performance of Super Express, Takuya was very different from the rest of the group on stage.
I can see it from the outside, but it's a very different kind of existence.
Did I do something wrong? No, no, no.
I can't help but follow it with my eyes.
And when they do come close, sometimes they just have a blank expression on their face.
And then it goes "bang." That's good, isn't it?
I think that is Takatani's great strength.
I felt that he could make people excited with just this casual expression.
I also felt a gap when we talked.
The other thing is that it is absolutely essential for us to entertain the fans who come to the show.
It's not easy. It was really tough at Corona.
I knew that I had to come all the way to the venue and spend the last two or three hours there.
It's pretty amazing that you're willing to give up your time to do something like that.
Live shows are really only for that day, so there's a distribution, but I'm not sure what the temperature is like there.
Only the people who are at the venue will know, so it's important to entertain them with everything you've got.
It's the most important part.
Then we asked ourselves what we should do to make them enjoy it carefully.
There's a production, there's a set list, and so on.
We had a lot of meetings and so on.
There are a lot of places to create.
We probably decide the setlist ourselves.
Is there some kind of staging or something in there?
Ushiozaki is in.
We'll make something together.
The members discuss during rehearsals what they think should be done better here and there.
I think Takuya is probably doing the same thing, but the costumes...
Oh, really? I'm doing the costumes. Yes, you are.
I can draw a rough sketch.
That's what's so great about it. How do you always proceed?
I can't draw.
I've tried many times to draw it.
Seriously, he has too much artistic flair.
So it's impossible.
After all, I had no choice but to verbally tell him about the photos, or the article museum, or the images, or the close-up photos.
It's amazing what you can rough out.
I studied it.
Is that so? In a manner of speaking.
Because there are five of us.
If you go suddenly, that's pretty much it.
Well, sure. It's a tough balancing act.
Lifetime. That's pretty much the direction and theme of it.
And then I'm building up an image of the costume.
Yes, I'm kind of talking to Shiozaki basically.
Recently, they've been telling me in great detail what kind of costumes they want.
Oh, really?
Then I'll draw a picture or something to go with it.
Where do you get your inspiration for these costume designs?
Basically from the collection, I guess.
The whole collection. Look at the look.
I've seen a lot of them skip a lot, so on the contrary, they can be used together.
So, I write about things that I think are surprisingly useful together with those that are already tense.
No, me too, from that collection, and also because I really like to drive, so when I'm driving and I see the city, and I'm like, "Oh, my God.
If I think her clothes are cute, I'll get it from there and use that pattern.
Oh, that's good. I see. Surprisingly, it's interesting.
even
I'll take a drive or something. I'll take a drive.
I like to drive, so I get out of it what I can, but I also get something out of it.
I'd like to be able to write rough drafts, too, though I'm thinking of doing it in the future.
I'm sure it'll turn out surprisingly well. Show me that rough sketch next time.
Yes, I draw with a pad. It's easier with a pad.
Oh, digital. Digital, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's cool. Go ahead, try it.
I'd bring my tablet to meetings and stuff.
I've always wanted to have one of those, but I don't use it for anything.
When? When. Yeah, you know, he's just trying to look cool.
It's like it's just there. It's like you're drawing it like this. Seriously.
No. No, really.
problem
I don't know what's troubling me.
The problems that cannot be told to members of the same group are
They say that's your job, so do that.
I'm seriously worried and annoyed.
A stiff one.
Wait a minute.
dismissal
a-ha-ha-ha (laughing loudly)
- Oh, it's you. - It's not me, miss.
- It wasn't me.
the night of the eight month of the lunar calendar